This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[IQIYI]
[Present]
♫Never met anyone who could make me understand this word♫
♫But when I met you, my heart started beating fast♫
♫You’re the only one in my heart who could make me feel this way♫
♫This long-awaitied moment is now over♫
♫From now on, my heart and soul will be yours for the rest of my life♫
♫Always have each other, never let go♫
♫Trust in me ‘cause I’ll be by your side♫
♫Hold my hand, Baby♫
[Desires in the Wind]
[Previously]
[Princess Blew]: Is this the line of rightness?
I’m afraid you and I, we…
I’ll cross the line to be with you, Miss Vayo.
[Fai]: If she’s the one, just go for it.
What are you waiting for?
What is my older sister, Fai, doing?
[Staff]: She’s already in bed, Miss.
[Criminals]: They know we’re here.
[Bua]: Lom!
Buahima, can you find someone to take me to Surat?
Fai!
Sis!
[Lom]: Hello.
[Fai]: Uncle Yod will take you to the island.
Uncle Boon will come pick you up when you’re there.
[Boonsong]: Hello, ladies.
Your place is ready but it’s at the end of the beach.
I’ll be Phatpha the way I want her to be.
And I’ll be Wind the way I want.
Your kind of Wind, what is she like?
I’ll just do whatever my heart says.
I will…
[Wind]: I will…will…
[Phatpha]: You will what?
[Phatpha]: Yes?
[Bua]: Wind!
So, did you have a good sleep last night?
Yes.
Look, all the food today is not spicy, exactly as requested.
I’ve also cooked only the food you like, Wind.
Stir-fried Malindjo Leaves with Egg, Sweet Pork, and Pork Spare Ribs Soup.
Hmm, but I never told you what I like.
I just guessed.
I know you like them, don’t you?
By the way, Dad wants me to invite you two to have dinner at our place this evening.
Dad brought home lots of fresh seafood this morning. Please be there, Wind.
Can I think about it first?
Sure. You’d better start eating, otherwise the food might get cold.
Or if you want me to feed you, you can just say it.
I’d be more than happy to do it.
I’m not hungry yet.
I’ll bring you the dishes once we finish eating.
Oh, no need. I’ll come collect them.
Or if you ever need anything, feel free to let me know.
Or if you want to see me after this,
I’m available 24-7. Always ready.
I’ll be back.
Is Miss Phatpha all right?
Go ahead and eat.
Why didn’t you invite Bua to eat with us too?
Maybe not.
She makes me feel awkward.
I thought you liked her.
No, not at all.
I’d rather be with someone I like.
About Uncle Boonsong’s dinner invitation, do you want to go?
Mhm, I should, as a matter of courtesy.
But you can tell me honestly if you don’t want to go.
I’ll turn down the invitation for you.
But if I don’t go, wouldn’t you feel bad?
No, why would I feel bad about it?
If I don’t go, you won’t be able to see…
See what?
Nothing. Let’s just say I’ll go.
Okay.
By the way, Aunt Paka just sent someone to bring us clothes.
She said they are what she wore when she was young.
If you have no problem wearing them, they’re all yours.
Can you really wear this?
Yes, it’s called Sarong.
The locals here wear them every day.
Then, should I wear it for tonight?
So that Aunt Paka would be happy.
Good idea.
But…how do you wear it? I have no clue.
I’ll teach you.
First, unfold it and hold it like this.
Then, shake and insert yourself in it.
♫I wonder which star it is that guided me to meet you♫
♫Or is it destiny…♫
Got it? Is it coming off?
♫That has brought us together♫
♫You’re like the wind, carrying me to the sky♫
♫No matter how high, I won’t be afraid♫
♫Only you is enough, I don’t need anything else♫
♫Just us together is enough, you’re the meaning in my life♫
♫Every day from now, please stay by my side and we’ll always have each other♫
[Phatpha]: Wind.
How do I look?
You look great.
As I thought, it looks perfect on you.
Really?
Yes, anything looks pretty on you.
Just like what they say, a good hanger can make the clothes shine.
A hanger?
The one in the house?
No, I mean the person who’s wearing it.
It’s a metaphor.
Thanks.
Shall we go then?
Otherwise, Bua might come to get us again.
I guess you sweet talk like this to everyone.
Miss Phat! Wind! What perfect timing.
The food is almost ready.
Thank you for having us. It’s very kind of you indeed.
Oh, you’re welcome.
It’s our pleasure indeed.
You look so beautiful in this dress, Miss Phatpha.
It’s your dress, Auntie.
Oh, but it looks great on you.
Oh my, Wind, look at you! Could you be any more handsome?
I've been like this since when I was born, Uncle.
Whoa, look at that. She’s got a good sense of humour too.
And Miss Phatpha, you look stunning in that outfit.
My wife didn’t look this pretty when she wore it.
You, Geezer. Watch your mouth!
Huh, when did you get here?
[Bua]: Since the beginning, Dad.
[Paka]: From the beginning.
Knowing you’ll be eating with us, I’ve put my best effort into cooking all the food today.
[Paka]: Geez, this girl.
[Bua]: Ouch. Mum!
Such a big talker. She’s only been here to help a while ago.
[Paka]: Seriously.
[Bua]: Mum! Don’t embarrass me in front of Wind like that. You’re ruining my reputation.
I’m not. I’m only stating the truth like your dad.
What’s there to be embarrassed about? It’s not like you have any reputation anyway.
Geez, Dad!
All right, why don’t you two go take a walk first?
I’ll let you know when the food is ready.
Okay.
Okay. Go on, give it your best shot.
Let’s go that way.
[Bua]: What, Dad?
[Boonsong]: What? Why are you looking at me?
I was looking at her, not you! Don’t get in the way.
[Paka]: You and your damn jar.
- So, it’s my fault, huh?
Make some chilli mash for me.
Go ahead, enjoy it!
[Paka]: This is delicious.
Miss Phatpha, can you eat them?
Yes.
Is it good?
Geez, Old Man. We’re eating here.
It’s rolling down my throat.
Is it that good?
Dead good. Eat up, girls.
[Boonsong]: She doesn’t know how to peel it.
Let me do it.
She’s good.
Remember that? It’s because of this crab peeling, that’s why we…
Stop! Don’t say it.
Are you two flirting again?
[Boonsong]: Just reminiscing about our past.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Wow, so good.
Good, right?
Is the food to your liking?
- Yes.
- Is the sauce too spicy?
- Yes, a bit spicy.
- Okay.
The food is amazing. They’re so fresh.
Yes.
The seafood here is really fresh. As for myself, I’m also fresh and single.
Dad, got something in your throat?
- Yeah.
- Really, my daughter.
If you like it, you can come join us every day.
It’s fun to eat with many people. Very lively and entertaining.
I’m already grateful enough for letting me stay here.
Oh, please don’t be.
Thank you.
Here.
Miss Wind, let’s go for a walk, shall we?
Sure.
Geez, Dad! She’s not done yet. Where are you going to take her?
This brat, it’s none of the kid’s business.
- Dad!
- So nosy!
I’ll go wait over there.
Oh dear, honey.
Seriously, can you even stand?
I’ll be back in a bit.
Yes.
Let me peel it for you, Miss Phatpha.
Thank you.
Peel more for her, dear.
Okay.
Miss Fai just called.
She said the suspect arrested in Chiang Rai is now dead.
Despite those men Dad sent to keep watch at the hospital, those traitors still found a way to silence him.
Miss Fai said the suspect refused to confess.
He got killed right after he was discharged.
I heard we also lost an officer this time.
We have no more witnesses left.
We must come up with a plan.
Miss Fai said whatever you want her to do, just say it.
She already has her people ready.
[Phone ringing]
Just a moment. It’s Miss Fai.
Can I answer it?
Yes, Fai?
[Bua]: Here, Mum.
- [Paka]: Thanks.
-  I’ll go wash the dishes first.
- Okay.
- Take care of her for me.
- Yes.
Pretty Miss Phatpha, may I ask you something?
What is it?
It’s about Wind.
Well, I…I…
I want to know if Wind already has a girlfriend or someone she likes yet.
If so, I’ll back off. But if not, I’m going to pursue her.
It’s just that Wind is exactly my type, as if the sea has specifically carried my soulmate to me on this island.
So, I really don’t want to let her slip away, Phat!
Why don’t you just ask her then?
Really, Miss Phat, who’d dare to ask her crush something like that?
Besides, you’re close to her.
I thought it might be better to ask someone close to her.
So, does Wind have anyone she likes yet?
Honestly, I also don’t know.
I just know that many girls are going after her, but she doesn’t seem to get serious with anyone.
So…is that a yes or no?
I really don’t know.
Then, can you ask her for me? Please, Miss Phat. Please.
I’ll ask her for you.
Oh, Miss Phat, you’re the sweetest indeed.
If I get to be Wind’s girlfriend, I’ll never forget it’s because of you. Thank you!
Yes.
What’s in that jar?
Oh, it’s a herbal liquor drink.
I’m telling you, once you drink it, your behaviour and personality will completely change.
It will make you feel jollier and more daring.
You’ll be bold enough to do something you usually never dare to do.
Does that kind of drink really exist?
Of course.
Look, do you want to try it, Miss Phat?
If you take a sip, you might be bold enough to ask Wind for me.
You traitors! I’ll have all of you executed!
You dare resist?
Traitors!
Phatpha!
What are you doing?
Get yourself together. Calm down!
Hey! Don’t touch me!
Traitor! Traitor! That’s a traitor too! Traitors!
Bua! Did you give her a liquor drink?
Yes, but just a sip though.
[Phatpha]: Traitors! Traitors!
[Boonsong]: Girl, are you sure it was just a sip?
[Bua]: Yep, one sip but many shots.
[Boonsong]: Geez!
I’ll take her home then.
Okay.
Come, let’s go home.
Hey! Don’t touch me, Traitors!
Let’s go home. Come on.
[Bua]: Stop! Traitors!
Traitors!
[Phatpha]: No! No! Don’t!
[Wind]: Let’s go home.
[Phatpha]: Don’t touch me! Stop!
[Bua]: What?
[Phatpha]: You traitors!
[Phatpha]: Stop!
[Wind]: Let’s go home.
Stop!
Be careful. Let’s go home.
[Wind]: Let’s go home. Let’s go.
[Phatpha]: Traitors! Traitors! Traitors!
[Phatpha]: Stop! No!
[Wind]: Let’s go home.
[Wind]: Let’s go home, Phat.
[Phatpha]: No! No! Traitors! Don’t! Don’t…
[Wind]: What to do then?
[Phatpha]: Stop! Stop!
Maybe we should let her sleep at my place tonight.
No! Traitor!
[Bua]: Let me go!
[Phatpha]: Don’t you dare touch me!
- You look after Bua, she’s already a handful.
- Are you sure?
Let’s go home. Yes, no problem.
Let’s go home.
Hey! Stop!
[Bua]: Wind, let me help! I’ll…
[Wind]: It’s okay!
Wind! Why did you yell at me?
[Wind]: Let’s go home.
[Phatpha]: Bad people!
[Boonsong]: Come here!
[Bua]: Wind yelled at me!
- [Boonsong]: Let’s go!
[Phatpha]: Traitors!
[Wind]: Just take Bua home.
[Boonsong]: You sure? Let’s go! Come on!
[Wind]: Come, let’s go home.
[Phatpha]: No!
Let’s go home. Come on. Let’s go home.
No! Don’t touch me! Stop!
Please hang in there. We’re almost home.
Are you okay?
No, I’m not.
Please hang in there. Just hang in there.
I’m poisoned.
Poison? What poison?
Yes, poison.
That drink is poisoned. Those traitors try to poison me!
Poisoned by the traitors?
It’s not poison. It’s a liquor drink. You’ll get better soon.
I’m dying. I’m not gonna make it.
Sure, you will. Definitely.
We’ve been through it this far. We’ll absolutely make it.
I’m well aware of the situation. This poison is fatal.
Please look after Madelin for me.
No, you have to look after it yourself. You will return to Madelin, Princess.
Return to Madelin?
Yes, return to Madelin.
But right now, I wish I could stay here forever.
Are you awake?
If you’re awake, please let go of my hand.
I’m sorry.
What happened last night
Why am I here?
Why can’t I remember anything?
What’s the last thing you remember about last night?
I remember I took some kind of drink.
That’s the beginning of it all.
Because of that drink?
Yes, it’s a herbal liquor drink–an extremely strong liquor.
I had no idea it was that strong.
Why did you drink it then?
I wanted to blend in with the locals on this island as much as I could.
Next time, if I’m not around, don’t accept any food or drink you’ve never tried before.
What if something bad happens to you?
Then, always stay with me.
Don’t ever leave my side, like when you’ve promised that you’ll protect me
Can you promise me…that you’ll never leave me alone again?
I promise. I will always stay by your side until you no longer need me.
How come it’s here?
Shall we go to sleep?
The weather is so nice. I want to dance with the prince first.
The prince? The prince is here too?
Good! Careful, you might fall.
Dance with me.
Or was it just a dream?
Last night, I got drunk and fell asleep, and didn’t do anything weird to you, did I?
That’s right. You fell asleep right away.
I see.
Or was I dreaming?
What dream?
Well, last night, I dreamt about something.
Was it a good dream or a bad dream?
Good, I guess.
What was it about? Can you tell me?
Nothing. That’s all.
Please watch where you’re going.
Where are you going?
Throw away the water.
Can you not go?
Just hold my hand and stay with me like this.
I don’t want to stay away from you, Wind. Please…
Auntie, can you please wash this for me too?
Thank you!
Hi, Miss Phat!
Are you sober now?
I just want to know how drunk I was last night.
Well, last night, you were incredibly drunk!
Hey, don’t worry.
Tell you what? My dad and mum are much worse than you when they get drunk. They’re so wasted.
Wasted?
It means being so drunk like this–Awooo! Drunk like a dog.
So, where are you off to, Miss Bua?
Oh, I’m heading off to work. I’ll go help the locals with their work.
What work?
Well, hauling in the net or catching fishes–those kinds of things.
Can I help too? I have nothing to do anyway.
Of course. But maybe you should…
Miss Blew? Miss Blew?
Where is she?
[Villager]: Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[Bua]: Are you okay, Miss Phat?
[Villager]: That’s right. Good job!
Phatpha! What are you doing?
Hauling in the net. Look, I caught some fish too.
You don’t have to do this.
But I have nothing to do.
I want to learn about their ways of living.
Can I spend time with them, Wind?
Of course, but I’ll be with you too.
NOOO! Don’t!
[Wind]: Put it away!
[Villagers]: Go, Miss Phat! Go, Miss Phat!
[Bua]: Oh, Miss Phat! There!
[Bua]: Well done, Wind!
[Bua]: Hey! I got it too! I got it! Yay!
[Bua]: Huh?
[Bua]: Yes.
[Phatpha]: Like this?
[Bua]: Pull it tight. Yes, like that.
That’s right. Then…okay, that’s correct.
[Phatpha]: Through this hole.
- Yes. Good job.
Wow!
Did I get it right?
Well done, girl.
[Phatpha]: This hole?
[Bua]: Yes.
[Phatpha]: Then here.
[Bua]: Correct.
Arrange them like this, Miss Phat.
Hello, children. Let’s learn some English today.
What is this?
‘Pla’.
Yes, and what is ‘Pla’ in English?
Fish!
Fish! How do you spell them?
F
I
S
H
[Phatpha]: How do you pronounce it?
[Children]: Fish!
[Phatpha]: Next, what is this?
[Children]: ‘Ruae’.
And what is ‘Ruae’ in English?
Boat!
Next, what is ‘Hua Roh’ in English?
Laugh!
Let me see you laugh, everyone!
[Laughters]
[Phatpha]: What we just did is called ‘laughing’.
I’m not having it.
Miss Phat, I just don’t want to walk around empty-handed. It’s not for you.
By the way, have you seen Wind?
I think she went to the loo. She’ll probably be back soon.
So, that thing I’ve asked you to help find out about Wind, is there any update?
Update on what?
Well, whether Wind already has someone she likes or not.
I guess you must be so drunk that night you couldn’t remember a thing.
But I already told you. I have absolutely no idea.
Come on, Miss Phat. If you don’t know, can’t you try to find out and ask her for me?
You and Wind are close friends.
She’ll definitely tell you whether she has someone she likes or not.
Please, Miss Phat. Please help me. Can you find out for me?
I…
[Wind]: I already have someone that I like.
W…Who is it? You’re lying. I don’t believe you.
It’s true. I already have someone that I like.
Very much too.
You’re so mean! Why do you have to be so blunt?
I don’t want to lead you on. I hope you'll understand.
No! I don’t!
Just you wait. From now on, I’ll never bring you food ever again.
Even Mum tells me so, I’m not going to do it.
Don’t you think it was too harsh?
Not at all. Let’s go home.
Let’s go.
The stars are so beautiful today.
That’s right, but not as beautiful as you.
Wind, I have a question.
What is it?
Do you always talk so sweetly like this to every girl in your life?
Sorry, if it seems rude or makes you feel uncomfortable, you don’t have to answer it.
Hold on.
Why did you ask me that? Is something bothering your mind?
I’m just curious. You told Bua you already have someone you like.
Oh! About that, it’s…
That woman is very lucky to have you in her life.
That woman?
How did you know I like girls?
I heard about it from Miss Lada.
If you already have someone you like, you should be more careful when you’re with other girls.
Don’t be so sweet to them.
They might misunderstand and get the wrong idea.
It’s you who are getting it wrong.
Getting what wrong?
Yes, I do like girls and I used to have a girlfriend. But I’m not seeing anyone right now.
I told Bua like that because I don’t want her to bother me.
That’s all.
I’ve made your life difficult, haven’t I?
I’ve made you lose chances to go out with those you might like.
No.
Once I return to Madelin, I’ll ask Father to grant you a reward for what you’ve done and sacrificed.
I never want anything in return for helping you.
But it’s something you deserve.
You can tell me if you want anything.
It’s the least I could do to feel less indebted to you.
What if what I want is something impossible?
There’s nothing Father can never grant for the person who has saved my life.
There is.
If I say it, it might cause me a grave punishment for not knowing my own place.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
So, have you ever been in love, Phatpha?
Since I was little, I’ve been helping Father with his work. I’m afraid I barely have time for love.
But when the time comes, you’ll finally find the right prince who can make you fall in love.
How do you know I like princes?
Because in every storytelling, a princess always ends up with a prince.
For me, it doesn’t always have to be like that.
Boss, after tracking that cop’s siblings for a while,
I think the princess and Vayo are definitely somewhere in Surat.
Then, hurry and find them before that bastard Henri will come b–
Boss! I’ve got some news about them.
Can I help?
It’s okay. Let me do it.
But I want to help.
That’s all right. Don’t forget you’re a princess, Phatph
It’s all right.
If you keep doing everything for me, I’d end up being so pampered soon.
Please let me help.
No.
Yes.
I’m sorry.
I…I’ll just go inside. Ouch!
Phatpha! Are you all right?
I’m okay.
Ouch!
Does it hurt?
Please wait here.
It’ll hurt a little.
Wind, Dad wants me to get you. He’s going to sail to shore.
Miss Phatpha, what’s wrong?
I was clumsy and got my ankle sprained.
Oh dear, that must have hurt a lot.
Does it feel better?
Don’t walk a lot today. It should get better tomorrow.
Wind, you’d better hurry. I’ll stay here to keep her company.
Are you sure you can do that?
Yes, just go now. I’m still hurt and don’t want to see your face for too long.
I’ll be back soon.
Does it hurt a lot?
Yes.
You’ll get better soon.
Hello, Uncle.
Oh, Miss Wind. I’m heading out for shore. Do you need anything?
Please carry this.
Please keep it, Miss. I don’t know how to use it.
Just take it, in case you might need it.
Okay then.
Please don’t worry. I’ll take care of everything.
Please be careful, Uncle.
Thank you.
You surprise me, Miss Phatpha. I never thought you’d know how to wash clothes–not to mention they’re this clean.
Wind did it for me.
Huh? Wind did all this for you?
Wow,
she’s very caring indeed.
Can’t believe I’ve been so stupid all this time.
Should’ve told me if you two are having a fling.
I’ve made such a complete fool of myself.
I don’t get it. What are you talking about?
About the person Wind likes, of course.
And I was wondering why you don’t want to tell me who it is that Wind likes.
That’s because I really don’t know. If I do, I would’ve told you long ago.
What?
Hold on. Do you really not know who it is that Wind likes?
You already know?
Geez, Miss Phat.
The whole island already knows about it. Acting lovey-dovey all the time like that, I wonder who wouldn’t know.
But I’m with her every day. How come I never know whom she likes?
Miss Phat, listen carefully.
The person she likes is you.
Wind likes me?
Yes! I’m only giving up on her because you’re prettier than me, and you’ve also met her before me.
Otherwise, I would’ve never backed down.
I think you’re misunderstanding something.
If you don’t believe me, just go and ask Wind.
[Bua]: The person Wind likes is you.
Phatpha.
Oh, you’re back?
Mhm.
Want some water?
[Bua]: If you don’t believe me, just go and ask Wind.
Phatpha, you’re overpouring.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Of course. I’m fine.
If you don’t tell me, I’m going to make Bua say it.
Please don’t!
It’s really nothing.
Do you know you’re bad at lying? It’s so obvious.
Well, there’s something I need to ponder about but I can’t tell you right now.
I’ll tell you later, okay?
Is it about Madelin?
Let’s just say it matters to me a lot.
Please don’t ask me right now.
I’ll tell you when I’m ready.
Is your foot better?
A bit.
[Yod]: Come, come. Careful there. Come and sit down first.
[Boonsong]: Not first then. It’s obviously after you.
So, how’s it going over there?
It’s good. She seems to fit in quite well.
Good. I’ll let Miss Fai know so she won't be worried.
Here, they’re all yours.
Whoa, what is it?
Miss Fai said it’s for them.
Wow, that’s a lot, isn’t it?
So, when are you leaving?
I guess tomorrow morning.
Oh, that’s your coffee. I ordered it for you.
Really? Thanks a lot.
Have a sip. It’s refreshing.
Thanks, it’s really hot today.
In Madelin, I often lie down like this and stargazing with Karel.
Our palace has a stargazing room with a glass ceiling.
Do you need a pillow? So that your neck won’t hurt
I’ll get it for you.
I’m good here.
Do you mind using my arm as a pillow instead?
I wonder how Father and Karel are doing right now.
Everything will be over soon.
When that time comes, I’ll take you back to Madelin myself.
[NEXT EPISODE]
Go! Slit up and search!
Over there.
[Boonsong]: The girl called Vayo you’re looking for.
Go get that brat and the princess. Quick!
If you ever see this message, run away immediately.
I’ve prepared a boat for us behind the bay.
Miss Blew, Lom told me to get you. We need to hurry.
There! They’re there! Go after them!
They’re right behind!
Miss Vayo, look out!
Lom!!
♫ I wonder which star it is that guided me to meet you ♫
♫Or is it destiny that has brought us together♫
♫You’re like the wind, carrying me to the sky♫
♫No matter how high, I won’t be afraid♫
♫ Only you is enough, I don’t need anything else ♫
♫ust us together is enough, you’re the meaning in my life♫
♫Every day from now, please stay by my side♫
[Desires in the Wind]
♫and we’ll always have each other♫
[North Star Entertainment]